A Guide to the International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) records FA084
Rockefeller Archive Center
- IBEC, 1946-1980; 8; 71.47 Cubic Feet 182 letter document boxes and 5 legal document boxes
  - Rockefeller Family, 1968-1976 (Box 301, Folder 1609)
    Correspondence, memorandum, magazine, report, article, summary, news clipping. Articles, comments about the Rockefeller family. Documents in this folder are in English and Spanish.
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1973-1975 (Box 301, Folder 1610)
    Correspondence, news clipping, article, newspaper, press release. Microfilmed. Documents in this folder are in English and German.
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Working Papers, 1974 (Box 302, Folder 1611)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1969-1976 (Box 302, Folder 1612)
    Correspondence, report, memorandum, telex, news clipping, speech, press release, magazine. News Clippings about Nelson's appointment as Vice President. Microfilmed (J6). Documents in this folder are in English and Spanish.
  - Rodopa, 1966-1972 (Box 302, Folder 1613)
  - Roi-Et Silk Mills Ltd., 1970-1973 (Box 302, Folder 1614)
    Correspondence, telex, cablegram, memorandum. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Rolibec, Inc. - Agencies - Africa, 1964 (Box 302, Folder 1615)
    Correspondence, directory. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Rolibec, Inc. - Agencies - Belgium, 1964-1966 (Box 302, Folder 1616)
  - IBEC - RBHSA - Argentina, 1960-1974 (Box 302, Folder 1617)
    Correspondence, balance, memorandum, telex, cablegram, telegram. Documents in this folder are in English and Spanish.
  - Rolibec, Inc. - Agencies, 1964-1971 (Box 302, Folder 1618)
    Correspondence, report, news clipping, directory, memorandum. Documents in this folder are in English and Portuguese.
  - Rolibec, Inc. - Brazil, 1970-1974 (Box 302, Folder 1619)
    Correspondence, telex, report, memorandum, power of attorney. Previous correspondence on microfilm. Documents in this folder are in English and Portuguese.
  - Rolibec, Inc. - Agencies - Canada, 1961-1964 (Box 303, Folder 1620)
    Correspondence, memorandum, directory. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Rolibec, Inc. - Agencies - Chile, 1969-1975 (Box 303, Folder 1621)
    Correspondence, report, telegram, directory, cablegram, memorandum. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Rolibec Ltda - Colombia, 1967-1973 (Box 303, Folder 1622)
    Correspondence, telex, cablegram, report, memorandum, minutes. Documents in this folder are in English and Spanish.
  - Rolibec, Inc. - England, 1961-1973 (Box 303, Folder 1623)
  - Rolibec, Inc. - Agencies - France, 1964-1966 (Box 303, Folder 1624)
  - Rolibec, Inc. - Agencies - Holland, 1961-1964 (Box 303, Folder 1625)
  - Rolibec, Inc. - Hong Kong, 1970-1973 (Box 303, Folder 1626)
    Correspondence, memorandum, balance, proposal. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Rolibec, Inc. - Illinois, 1961-1974 (Box 303, Folder 1627)
    Correspondence, telex, summary, chart, draft, report, annual report, brochure, prospectus, memorandum. Documents in this folder are in English and Spanish.
  - Rolibec, Inc. - Agencies - Malaya and Singapore, 1961-1972 (Box 303, Folder 1628)
  - Rolibec, Inc. - Agencies - Puerto Rico, 1960-1972 (Box 303, Folder 1629)
    Correspondence, memorandum, news clipping, report, balance, telex, directory. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Rolibec, Inc. - Agencies - Mexico, 1962-1970 (Box 304, Folder 1630)
    Correspondence, cablegram, memorandum, directory. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Rolibec International Ltd., S. A. - Pan Planning - Okinawa, 1970 (Box 304, Folder 1631)
    Correspondence, telegram. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Rolibec International Ltd., S. A. - Panama, 1970-1973 (Box 304, Folder 1632)
    Correspondence, balance, report, memorandum. Previous correspondence on microfilm. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Rolibec International Ltd., S. A. - Latin American Division, 1963-1973 (Box 304, Folder 1633)
  - Rolibec - Japan, 1965-1973 (Box 304, Folder 1634)
    Correspondence, memorandum, cablegram, agreement, chart, news clipping, report. Previous correspondence on microfilm. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Rolibec - Korea, 1971-1973 (Box 304, Folder 1635)
    Correspondence, telex, report. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Rolibec, Inc. - Port of New York Authority, 1958 (Box 304, Folder 1636)
  - Rolibec Peru, S. A. - Peru, 1970-1973 (Box 304, Folder 1637)
    Correspondence, memorandum, telex, balance, report. Documents in this folder are in English and Spanish.
  - Rolibec, Inc. - Peru Branch - Peru, 1970-1973 (Box 304, Folder 1638)
    Correspondence, report, memorandum, balance, news clipping, telex. Update folder. Previous correspondence on microfilm. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Rolibec, Inc. - San Francisco Agency, 1967 (Box 304, Folder 1639)
    Correspondence, telegram, telex. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Rolibec International Ltda, S. A. - Thailand Brand, 1965-1974 (Box 305, Folder 1640)
    Correspondence, brochure, minutes, telex, memorandum, report, cablegram, balance. Previous correspondence on microfilm. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Rolibec International (Thailand) Ltd. Thailand, 1965-1974 (Box 305, Folder 1641)
    Correspondence, telex, telegram, certificate, memorandum, report. Previous correspondence on microfilm. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Rolibec - Venezuela, 1967-1974 (Box 305, Folder 1642)
    Correspondence, telex, memorandum, report, news clipping, minutes, annual report. Previous correspondence on microfilm. Documents in this folder are in English and Spanish.
  - Rolibec International Ltd., S. A. - Japan Branch, 1963-1973 (Box 305, Folder 1643)
    Correspondence, report, proposal, memorandum. Previous correspondence microfilmed. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Ross - United States - Ross Poultry Breeders, 1972-1977 (Box 305, Folder 1644)
    Correspondence, telex, memorandum, power of attorney, agreement, certificate, newsletter. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Rough Hill (Farm) Ltd. - United Kingdom, 1973 (Box 305, Folder 1645)
  - Sal Chile Limitada - Chile, 1964 (Box 305, Folder 1646)
    Brochure, cablegram, draft. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - San Felix de Inversiones CA - Venezuela, 1970-1975 (Box 306, Folder 1647)
    Correspondence, report, minutes. Previous correspondence on microfilm. Documents in this folder are in English and Spanish.
  - San Juan Apartment Corporation, 1959-1961 (Box 306, Folder 1648)
  - Sementes Agroceres, S. A. (SASA), 1971-1977 (Box 306, Folder 1649)
    Correspondence, telex, agreement, memorandum, draft, balance, summary, article, report. Previous correspondence on microfilm. Documents in this folder are in English and Portuguese.
  - Sementes Agroceres, S. A. (SASA), 1967-1970 (Box 307, Folder 1650)
    Correspondence, memorandum, telex, report, chart, article, balance, cablegram, news clipping. Information about 25th anniversary celebration of Sementes Agroceres. General Information. Previous correspondence on microfilm. Documents in this folder are in English and Portuguese.
  - Sementes Agroceres, S. A. (SASA) - Tab File #2 - Projects, 1968-1975 (Box 307, Folder 1651)
    Correspondence, report, summary, memorandum, telex, brochure, article. Information about projects in Brazil: Brazilian Hog project, sorghum, corn, opaque, rural nutrition, legumes. Documents in this folder are in English, Portuguese and Spanish.
  - Sementes Agroceres, S. A. (SASA) - Tab File #1, 1968-1975 (Box 308, Folder 1652)
    Correspondence, draft, cablegram, report, bulletin, chart, catalogue, telex, article. Information about projects: pre-cooked beans, planning expansion of British Honduras Poultry. Documents in this folder are in English and Portuguese.
  - Sementes Agroceres, S. A. (SASA) - Publicity, 1969-1975 (Box 308, Folder 1653)
    Correspondence, memorandum, article, report, news clipping, journal, telex. Previous correspondence on microfilm. Documents in this folder are in English and Portuguese.
  - Sementes Agroceres, S. A. (SASA) - Public Relations - 25th Anniversary, 1947-1970 (Box 308, Folder 1654)
    Correspondence, article, speech, report, summary, memorandum, draft, brochure, magazine. Agroceres Anniversary publicity package. Microfilmed? Documents in this folder are in English, Portuguese and Spanish.
  - Sementes Agroceres, S. A. (SASA) - Brazil - Publicity, 1971-1972 (Box 309, Folder 1655)
    Correspondence, report. Information about impact study SASA. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Sementes Agroceres, S. A. (SASA) - Brazil - Publicity - Brochures, Maps, Etc., 1947-1976 (Box 309, Folder 1656)
    Brochure, catalogue, memorandum, news clipping, newspaper, newsletter, chart, article, magazine, speech, advertisement, report, booklet. Documents in this folder are in English, Portuguese and Spanish.
  - Sementes Agroceres, S. A. (SASA) - Brazil - Publicity - Brochures, Maps, Etc., 1947-1976 (Box 310, Folder 1656A)
  - Sementes Horticeres, S. A. - Brazil, 1970-1972 (Box 310, Folder 1657)
    Correspondence, memorandum, report. Market Survey. Previous correspondence on microfilm. Documents in this folder are in English and Portuguese.
  - Serfige, S. A. - Spain, 1970-1975 (Box 310, Folder 1658)
    Correspondence, draft, newsletter, catalogue, press release, telex. Microfilmed. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Siam Cement - Annual Reports, 1953-1963 (Box 311, Folder 1659)
    Correspondence, balance, annual report. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Sinclair Collins - Division of IBEC, 1958 (Box 311, Folder 1660)
    Correspondence, draft. Previous correspondence on microfilm. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Sinclair Collins Valve, Etal, 1958-1975 (Box 311, Folder 1661)
    Correspondence, memorandum, receipts, report. Certificate of dissolution of Sinclair Collins Valve Company. "Handed over by Account Department after Central Records had filmed their files." Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Sixty Fifth Infantry, 1971-1973 (Box 311, Folder 1662)
    Correspondence, memorandum. Information about Puerto Rico shopping centers. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Societe Libanaise d'Expansion Avicola SAL (SLEA), 1968-1970 (Box 311, Folder 1663)
  - Structural Concrete Products Corporation - Puerto Rico, 1961-1968 (Box 311, Folder 1664)
    Correspondence, memorandum. Legal information. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - THAIBEC, 1970-1974 (Box 311, Folder 1665)
    Correspondence, memorandum, report, power of attorney, certificate, news clipping, proxy. Microfilmed. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Thai Celadon, 1960 (Box 311, Folder 1666)
    Brochure, memorandum. Articles of Association. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Thai Coconut Industries (TCI) - Correspondence and Finance, 1963-1970 (Box 311, Folder 1667)
    Correspondence, summary, cablegram, minutes, agreement, report, brochure, memorandum, telegram, telex. All previous correspondence on microfilm. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Thai Industrial Advancement Company Ltd. (TIAC), 1960-1972 (Box 311, Folder 1668)
    Correspondence, memorandum, catalogue, brochure. Other copies have been microfilmed. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - TIF - Thai Divest Fund, 1963-1973 (Box 312, Folder 1669)
    Correspondence, memorandum, report, telex, news clipping, brochure, annual report, news clipping, advertisement, catalogue. Information about planning in Hong Kong. Has been microfilmed. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Copesa/Todos - Peru, 1972-1976 (Box 312, Folder 1670)
    Correspondence, telex, balance, report, certificate, memorandum, cablegram. Previous correspondence on microfilm. Documents in this folder are in English and Spanish.
  - Copesa/Todos - Peru, 1971-1972 (Box 313, Folder 1671)
    Correspondence, report, telegram, telex, memorandum, cablegram. Legal information. Previous correspondence on microfilm. Documents in this folder are in English and Spanish.
  - Copesa/Todos, 1966-1970 (Box 313, Folder 1672)
    Correspondence, news clipping, draft, report, memorandum, telex. Examination of financial statements. Previous correspondence has been microfilmed. Documents in this folder are in English and Spanish.
  - Copesa/Todos - Tab File, 1969-1975 (Box 314, Folder 1673)
    Correspondence, memorandum, news clipping, report, agreement, telex, contract. Previous correspondence has been microfilmed. Documents in this folder are in English and Spanish.
  - Todos CA - Venezuela, 1960-1974 (Box 314, Folder 1674)
    Correspondence, minutes, report, annual report. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Copesa-Todos - Peru - Public Relations - Publicity, 1955-1973 (Box 314, Folder 1675)
    Correspondence, report, memorandum, magazine, news clipping, bulletin, advertisement, article, plans. Sent to microfilm unlimited. Documents in this folder are in English and Spanish.
  - Todos, S. A. - Reports, 1970-1972 (Box 314, Folder 1676)
    Correspondence, report, telex, memorandum. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Todos - Peru - Correspondence, 1954-1957 (Box 314, Folder 1677)
    Correspondence, minutes, balance, report, draft. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Todos, Inc. - Puerto Rico, 1956-1957 (Box 314, Folder 1678)
  - Todos Venezuela, 1953-1957 (Box 315, Folder 1679)
    Correspondence, balance, memorandum. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Copesa, 1954-1957 (Box 315, Folder 1680)
    Correspondence, memorandum, minutes, balance, report. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Coptosa, 1957-1959 (Box 315, Folder 1681)
    Correspondence, memorandum. Filmed. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Coptosa, 1954-1955 (Box 315, Folder 1682)
    Balance, report. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Todos, S. A. - Peru, 1957-1969 (Box 315, Folder 1683)
    Report, map, plans, news clipping. Documents in this folder are in English and Spanish.
  - Toledo Bellows - Correspondence and Finance, 1971-1976 (Box 315, Folder 1684)
    Correspondence, summary, advertisement, balance, memorandum, contract. Financial report. Previous correspondence on microfilm. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Toledo Bellows - Correspondence and Finance, 1968-1970 (Box 315, Folder 1685)
    Correspondence, memorandum, report, telex, cablegram, telegram, draft, balance. All previous correspondence to microfilm. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Toledo Bellows - Tab File, 1969-1975 (Box 316, Folder 1686)
    Correspondence, balance, memorandum, report, contract, catalogue, plans. Previous correspondence on microfilm. Documents in this folder are in English and Portuguese.
  - Transfactor, S. A. - Spain, 1973-1975 (Box 316, Folder 1687)
    Correspondence, cablegram, memorandum, brochure, press release, telex. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Transleasing, S. A. - Spain, 1973-1974 (Box 316, Folder 1688)
    Correspondence, telex, minutes, balance, report, brochure, memorandum. Documents in this folder are in English and Spanish.
  - Transoceanic Fishing Corporation Ltd. (TAOFC), 1973 (Box 316, Folder 1689)
    Correspondence, memorandum, report, draft. Legal information. Previous correspondence microfilmed. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Transoceanic Fishing Corporation Ltd. (TAOFC) - Public Relations, 1958-1960 (Box 316, Folder 1690)
    Correspondence, memorandum, press release, article, brochure, annual report. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Transoceanic Fishing Corporation Ltd. (TAOFC) - Public Relations, 1966-1974 (Box 316, Folder 1691)
    Correspondence, telex, memorandum, minutes, report, balance, summary, agreement. Microfilmed. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Transoceanic Insurance Co., 1958-1972 (Box 316, Folder 1692)
    Correspondence, memorandum, annual report, plans. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Fondo Tre R - Italy, 1969-1972 (Box 317, Folder 1693)
    Correspondence, article, telex, draft, agreement, prospectus, brochure, report, annual report, brochure. Microfilmed. Documents in this folder are in English and Italian.
  - Triarch Corporation Ltd., 1970-1972 (Box 317, Folder 1694)
  - Trimak, S. A. - Madrid, Spain - Correspondence and Finance, 1968-1971 (Box 317, Folder 1695)
    Correspondence, memorandum, agreement, report. Information about legal, patents. Previous financial correspondence has been microfilmed. Documents in this folder are in English and Spanish.
  - Operations - Utrillon - Manufacturing - Sales, Undated (Box 317, Folder 1696)
    See folder Projects and Proposals - Venezuela.
  - Valvair Corporation, 1958-1975 (Box 317, Folder 1697)
    Correspondence, report, telex, draft, memorandum, certificate. "Account dept. had filmed their file." Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Valvair - Holland - N.V., 1958-1960 (Box 317, Folder 1698)
  - Vanarbor, SPA - Oliveri, Sicily, 1966-1970 (Box 317, Folder 1699)
    Correspondence, photograph, telex. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Venezuela Basic Economy Corporation (VBEC) - Annual Reports, 1947-1952 (Box 317, Folder 1700)
    Annual report. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Well Cargo Inc. - Nevada, 1969 (Box 317, Folder 1701)
    Catalogue, report. Microfilmed. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Wells Overseas Limited - Peru, 1967-1969 (Box 317, Folder 1702)
    Correspondence, report. Consolidated Financial Statements. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Wells Overseas Limited - Canada, 1970-1975 (Box 317, Folder 1703)
    Correspondence, memorandum, draft, telex, agreement, power of attorney. Previous correspondence being microfilmed. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Wells Overseas Ltd. - Statements - Toronto, Canada, 1956-1968 (Box 318, Folder 1704)
    Correspondence, balance, memorandum, report. Consolidated Financial Statements. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Wells Overseas Ltd. - Peru, 1967-1975 (Box 318, Folder 1705)
    Correspondence, memorandum, report, telex, agreement, power of attorney, proxy, chart. Legal information. Has been microfilm, all previous correspondence on roll film (TAOFC-AOFC roll film). Documents in this folder are in English and Spanish.
  - Wells Overseas Limited - Peru, 1966-1968 (Box 319, Folder 1706)
    Correspondence, memorandum, report, draft, photograph. Microfilmed. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Wells de Venezuela, SRL - Venezuela - Correspondence and Finance, 1968-1972 (Box 319, Folder 1707)
    Correspondence, agreement, balance, memorandum, telex. Documents in this folder are in English and Spanish.
  - Wells de Venezuela, SRL - Venezuela - Tab File, 1969-1975 (Box 319, Folder 1708)
    Correspondence, minutes, agreement. Documents in this folder are in English and Spanish.
  - Willmott Electric, 1966-1974 (Box 319, Folder 1709)
    Correspondence, press release, memorandum, minutes, card, receipts, report, catalogue, annual report, brochure, agreement, balance. Information relating to Bellows Sign Co. Previous correspondence on microfilm. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - IBEC Operating Groups - Food and Housing Studies - Seeds - By Countries - Iran, 1970-1972 (Box 320, Folder 1710)
    Correspondence, report, summary, memorandum, telex, draft, news clipping, cablegram. Documents in this folder are in English and Portuguese.
  - IBEC Operating Groups - Food and Housing Studies - Seeds - Philippines, 1965-1970 (Box 321, Folder 1711)
    Correspondence, news clipping, report, article, newsletter, bulletin, draft, cablegram, telex, memorandum. Documents in this folder are in English and Spanish.
  - IBEC Operating Groups - Supermarket Division - Studies - San Juan Retail Market, 1971 (Box 321, Folder 1712)
  - IBEC Operating Groups - Supermarket Division - Tab File, 1964-1972 (Box 321, Folder 1713)
    Correspondence, memorandum, report, telex, balance. Information about publicity, operating reports, operating group supermarkets, training program, equipment and supplies, advisory board, meetings, legal, staff, insurance, bakeries, cash planning, consultants, supermarket study group. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - IBEC Operating Groups - Supermarket Division, 1965-1973 (Box 322, Folder 1714)
    Correspondence, memorandum, press release, report, cablegram, balance. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - IBEC Operating Groups - Textile Division, 1968-1974 (Box 322, Folder 1715)
    Correspondence, memorandum, telex, cablegram, report, balance. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Studies, 1963-1971 (Box 322, Folder 1716)
    Report, brochure, annual report. Documents in this folder are in English and Spanish.
  - IBEC Operating Groups - Studies - Food Task Force, 1967-1973 (Box 323, Folder 1717)
    Correspondence, memorandum, report, news clipping, draft, balance, article. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - IBEC Operating Groups - Studies - Seeds - Central America, 1969-1971 (Box 324, Folder 1718)
    Correspondence, report, memorandum, summary, balance, article, telex. Documents in this folder are in English and Spanish.
  - Fall Workshop, 1969 (Box 325, Folder 1719)
  - Fall Workshop, 1970 (Box 325, Folder 1720)
- IBEC History Project Files, 1942-1987; 9; 5.27 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes and 2 microfilm boxes
  This series contains general information about IBEC and its subsidiaries: annual reports, audited financial statements, financial analysis, stockholders meetings, operations, studies, transcripts of interviews with staff members, and also data regarding the sales and acquisitions of companies. Most of the material in this series is in English.
  - Summary - IBEC History Project Files, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Information about the files. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Microfiche Directory, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Information about microfiche. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - IBEC T-AOFC Prospectus - May 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, report, prospectus. Information about IBEC's prospectus in 1961. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Form S-1 IBEC - Registration Statement, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Prospectus. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Form 10 K - IBEC, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Form 10 K - IBEC - Extra Copies, 1974-1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Form 10 K - IBEC, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Report, certificate, correspondence, proxy, memorandum, telegram. Documents in this folder are in English.
  - Form 10 K - IBEC, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - IBEC - Thrift Plan Prospectus, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - IBEC - Audited Financial Statements, 1947-1954 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - IBEC - Audited Financial Statements, 1947-1954 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation (VBEC) - Caracas Branch - Audited Financial Statements, 1948-1953 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Automercado, C. A. - Audited Financial Statements, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Compania Anomina Distribuidora de Alimentos (CADA) - Audited Financial Statements, 1948-1953 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - C. A. Palotal - Audited Financial Statements, 1949-1954 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - C. A. Todos - Audited Financial Statements, 1948-1952 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Minimax C. A. - Audited Financial Statements, 1950-1953 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Productora Agro Pecuaria, Compania Anomina (PACA) - Audited Financial Statements, 1948-1953 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - PESCA - Audited Financial Statements, 1948-1957 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Via Lactea, C. A. - Audited Financial Statements, 1950-1954 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - IBEC Annual Reports, 1947-1949 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - IBEC Annual Reports, 1950-1954 (Box 1, Folder 22)